### About me

I'm a ZCPE (Zend Certified PHP Engineer) and I've worked with PHP since 2009, I'm passionate for open-source, patterns, tests and source code well written. Always looking for best practices, new technologies and methodologies to improve my workflow and bring great results to the project and to my customer.

#### Skills

Languages, Tools and Technologies				Certifications
<ul><li>PHP</li><li>MVC/MVVM</li><li>Zend</li><li>Symfony</li><li>Silex</li><li>Laravel</li></ul>	<ul><li>Wordpress</li><li>PHPUnit</li><li>Doctrine</li><li>Vagrant</li><li>Apache</li><li>MySQL</li></ul>	<ul><li>Grunt</li><li>Git</li><li>SVN</li><li>Windows</li><li>Linux</li><li>OSX</li></ul>	<ul><li>Javascript</li><li>jQuery</li><li>Angular</li><li>HTML/CSS/Less</li><li>TwitterBootstra</li><li>Java</li></ul>	

# Experience

FlixBus GmbH PHP Engineer Currently

• Changing the life of approximately one billion of people commuting, spending their weekends, building remote relationships, visiting relatives, and discovering the world.

NeoGrid Senior PHP Developer 2015 - 2017

- Created a web application using Material Design and AngularJS to the front-end and Silex to the back-end, which automated the sales of the WebEDI solution;
- Implemented improvements, bug fixes and integrations with NeoGrid solutions using REST APIs;
- Added the Vagrant tool to use with my team in order to use environments identical with the production environment;
- Evangelist of best practices of programming following the existent PSRs and implementing unit test in the projects;
- Reference in my team to projects that was written in PHP and AngularJS.

Humantech PHP Developer 2015 - 2015

- Led the team (five workers) as assistant manager of the programming department when the manager was not present:
- Added unit tests in critical project parts, reducing considerable the amount of bugs and increasing the quality of projects;
- Created an e-learning platform using the gamification concepts.

A2C PHP Developer 2013 - 2014

- Created a CMS to the 3M brand using the gamification concepts and fully focused on SEO, that resulted in three times more access to the website in few months;
- Created a software to monitor the reputation of political candidates in social networks, that give more visibility on medias to the agency;
- Reference in my team to projects that was written in Symfony 2;
- Responsible to manage the Amazon Web Services EC2, RDS and S3.

#### Education

- Honor as the best student of the course;
- The final paper is based on a tool created to be used by professionals that are studying to achieve the ZCPE certification, the project is open-source and is available on GitHub, the project is hosted by "DigitalOcean" as a sponsor.

# Courses

English Live Reaching fluency Currently

• I'm having classes with a private teacher about a lot of topics to be fluent discussing anything.